这个星期第二回了...
This is the second time this week...
就因为他要加班 我不得不去请个保姆
I had to pay for a sitter 'cause he was working late.
他挣那么多 这钱你们出得起啦
With all that money he make, you can afford it.
上帝
Lord.
怎么样啊 Bubs
What's up, Bubs?
嗨
Hey.
就是这儿了
There you go.
- 你有什么? - 一些"开胃粉"
- What you got? - I got some starters.
火线重案组 第一季 第十集 代价
The Wire S01E10 The Cost
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"然后他扔下了手铐..."  ---Greggs
是我的错 A(Avon)
My fault, A.
就不该留下你一个人 哥们
Should've never left you alone, homie.
不是的 该死
No, shit.
要不是你停车下来 我都不在了
Man, you ain't pull up when you did, I'm gone.
听着 我想知道我们几时能 向那个舔鸡巴的混蛋复仇?
Listen, what I want to know is how we fucking come back on this cocksucker?
不 现在不行
We don't. Not now.
听明白了吗?
You feel me?
听着 Stringer 你的建议很好...
Listen, Stringer, your advice was good advice...
你知道我的意思吧? 我要你明白
You know what I'm saying? I wanna let you know that.
我现在要你放出风声去
What I want you to do now is put the word out there.
让他知道 如果他愿意 我们可以把恩怨扯平了
I want you to let him know we willing to squash this, if he is.
那要是他不肯呢?
And then what the fuck if he ain't?
不会的 这黑鬼也住在这城里 我们要是跟他谈判 他还是得听的
No, this nigger live in the town, too. He gonna listen, if we parley.
然后他就会爬出洞来什么的
And then when he creep out of his hole, and shit.
- "砰" - 好啊
- Boom. - Okay.
- 干了他 - 别再说了 我明白了
- Smoke him. - Say no more, got you.
- 把话传出去 - 好的
- Put that out there, yo. - All right.
比赛结束之后 你是不是被警察跟踪了?
About them police, though, they was on your ass after the game?
嗯 好像被跟了两辆
Yeah, man, it was like two cars.
听着 要是他们盯上你了 就知道你的名字
See, if they on you, then they got a name.
要是有你的名字 就知道你没有驾照
If they got a name, then they know you got no license.
但他们要的不是交通违章罪 知道我在说什么吗?
But they don't want no traffic charges, you know what I'm saying?
他们才不在乎这种小罪名
They don't want no humble shit.
我想他们是要看看我会上哪儿去
I think they was trying to see where I might go.
你把他们带到哪个鬼地方去了?
Where the fuck was you gonna take their asses?
我带他们去了理发店
I was taking them to the barbershop.
真的 我是打算去剃个头
I was going to get a haircut.
改头换面?
Get a fade?
我知道 可这些狗娘养的盯上咱了 操
I know, B, but these motherfuckers are on us. Fuck.
他们一直都在盯我们 小心点就行了
They always have been on us, we just gotta be careful.
你别再打电话了
You not been talking on any phones.
也别掺和毒品的事了
And you not been touching any drugs.
从现在开始 钱的事你也别管了
And from now on, you are not doing the money runs.
我跟Bey来负责那档子事 等风头过了再说
Me and Bey, we gonna take care of that shit until this whole thing cool off.
把呼机给我
Let me get that pager.
怎么了 来真的啊?
What's up, you serious?
真的 我只给你一个纽约上家的号码
Serious. I'm gonna get you a New York supply number only.
要是本地的猫猫狗狗要找你
Any of these motherfucking local cats  wanna talk to you,
就得过我这关
They gotta talk to me.
我们要把你保护起来 哥们
We gotta build a wall around you, B.
再监听一个月 还是全新的号码 ?
Another month on a fresh phone?
平房区的公用电话都被拆了
They ripped out the pay phones in the low-rises.
现在他们打电话得走到一两个街区外
Now they're walking a block or two.
还要多久你才能把这案子结了 Jimmy?
How much longer until you bring this case in?
越快了结对大家就越好 也包括你
The quicker you can the better for everybody. Yourself included.
看看这个
Look at this.
Gwynn法官说很抱歉
Judge Gwynn sends his regrets.
没法共进午餐了
He can't make lunch.
活像我得了瘟疫一样 躲之不及 给你 新电话
Like I suddenly got the plague. There's your new phone.
30天
30 days.
几周前 Burrell想终止监听的时候
A few weeks ago, when Burrell wanted to take down the wire
你他妈的气得要打爆他的屁眼
You were the one breaking off on his ass.
Jimmy 这儿可有位女士
Jimmy, there's a lady here.
Rhonda比我们更会爆粗口呢 法官大人
Rhonda talks more trash than both of us, Your Honor.
我一直都是个淑女 法官大人
I have never been anything other than ladylike, Your Honor.
McNulty警官很过分地冒犯了一位法庭官员
Detective McNulty is going out of his way to insult an officer of the court.
- McNulty 我要判你藐视法庭罪 - 谁不是呢?
- McNulty, I hold you in contempt. - Who doesn't?
他怎么了?
What's with him?
- 你没听说吗? - 没
- You haven't heard? - No.
- 这些照片有啥不对劲? - 不知道
- What's wrong with the picture? - Don't know.
助选晚宴
Phelan不在里头
Phelan isn't in it.
什么 他要竞选吗?
What, he's up for election?
我还以为法官的任期是15年呢
I thought judges had 15-year terms.
没错 不过Phelan是被提名 做Halpern的继任者...
They do, but Phelan was named to finish Halpern's term...
现在只剩两年了
Which only had two years left.
所以他首先要搞好自己的初选
So he has to run on his own in the primary.
什么 他不在选票上?
What, he's not on the ticket?
为什么没啊?
Why the fuck not?
也许是因为所交非人吧
Maybe it's the company he keeps.
见鬼
Fuck.
不 你没考虑小孩会需要多大空间
No, see, you ain't thinking about how much room the baby gonna need.
特别是当他开始长大...
Specially when he get to growing...
因为有些东西是非要不可的
'cause there are things we got to have.
比如一张真正的婴儿床 一张游戏桌...
Like a real crib, a play desk...
还得有一辆"小泰克"的电动车
And you know, he got to have one of them Little Tikes cars.
我不是说你的住处不够好...
I'm not saying your place ain't nice enough...
对你来说已经够好了 可要是我们成个家...
'cause for you, it do just fine, but if we gonna be a family...
那就算我们不要多两个房间 至少也得多一个
We need at least one more room, if not two.
这样才能添些卧室家私
So you add the bedroom set,
就像Howard大街那家婴儿用品店里 那样漂亮的全套卧室家私
A nice bedroom set like the one they got down at that baby store on Howard Street,
可是一整个房间呢
And that's a room right there.
我们也许还能弄些更好的家具...
And I think we might get some better furniture...
把你的东西放到另一间卧室去...
And put your stuff in the other bedroom...
就像一个工作间...
Iike it was a den...
你的沙发以前倒是挺新潮的...
'cause the sofa you got seen better days...
我想你都知道的
I think you know that much.
Dee 你要去哪儿
Dee, where you going at?
我跟你说了 我要钱买新的卧室套装
I told you I need money for the new bedroom set.
Dee!
- 你呼我干嘛? - 唷 我们手头紧了
- Why you holler at me? - Yo, man, we getting down to it.
时候到了 会来找你
I get to you when I get to you.
这个是老窝
That's the main stash house.
什么?
Say what?
打进电话的是为Barksdale运作老窝的人
The incoming call is the guy who runs the main stash for Barksdale's people.
- 是谁? - 我们不知道
- Who is he? - We don't know.
这么说 你们只是猜测他是在老窝里?
So, y'all are just guessing he's on the stash, right?
不是猜的 他就在那儿
No, he's on it.
Lester检查记录的时候发现了这个模式
Lester was checking the logs when he picked up the pattern.
每次他们的货卖得差不多的时候...
Every time they get down to the ends on a package...
楼里就有人会打那个呼机号
Somebody in the tower hits that pager number.
然后 半个小时之内 每一次...
Then, within a half-hour every fucking time...
都有一个来自Pimlico的号码 打到大楼那儿的公用电话
A call comes back to the tower pay phone from that number in Pimlico.
哪个?
Which is?
在Cold Spring道Reisterstown那里 Mondo超市的一个公用电话
It's a pay phone at a Mondo Mart in Reisterstown on Cold Spring Lane.
看到了?
You see it now?
存货不足的时候
When the supply gets low,
他们就呼叫这个混蛋...
They page this mope...
而他总是会从西北端一个公用电话回电
Who always calls back from a pay phone way the fuck out in north-west.
同一个电话 同样的模式
Same phone, same pattern.
所以你们都觉得 他接收补货的申请...
So y'all think that he's taking the re-up order...
而窝点就在Mondo超市附近 对吧?
And that the stash is somewhere near the Mondo Mart, right?
你说对了 Sydnor警官
You are on it, Detective Sydnor.
好吧 你们打算怎么干?
Okay, so what do you do with this?
我们怎么干?
What do we do?
我们要监听Pimlico的这个电话...
We're gonna be sitting on that phone in Pimlico...
24小时不间断 在Mondo超市等着
All day and night waiting on Mr. Mondo Mart.
- 还有Herc - Herc这整周都来不了
- Herc, too. - Herc's out this whole week.
- 参加在职培训 - 太糟了
- In-service training. - That's too bad.
所以就不是8小时一班的三班倒了 你们俩每人要值12小时
So, instead of three eight-hour shifts, you two are gonna have to pull 1 2 hours.
直接杀了我得了
Just fucking kill me now.
有Omar的消息吗?
Heard from Omar?
没有
Nope.
我要去惊动惊动他 你要去哪儿?
I'm gonna go try to scare him up. Where you gonna be?
电话里头的人都在谈论...
Everyone on the wire keeps talking about...
说这孩子为了那死去的劫匪男孩伤心欲绝
How this kid's all tore up about the dead stickup boy.
我打算亲自去瞧瞧
I'm gonna see for myself.
好的
All right.
- 需要我们的话 就用无线电呼叫 - 行
- You need us, we're on the radio. - Okay.
嘿 怎么样 伙计?
Hey, what up, man?
这头一回 我可以要四盎司可卡因...
This first time, I can go four ounces of rock...
要是货能对版 下次我可以要多些
But hey, if the shit is right, then next time I can step that up.
就四盎司不值得这么搞
Almost ain't worth it for four.
这只是头一回嘛
Just this first go-round.
你们要是不糊弄我 我会当回头客的
You do right by me, I'll turn around and come back on it.
你的钱呢 伙计?
Where your money at, man?
行了
We good.
那么 东西呢?
So, where the shit at?
除了你 没人来过这里 没人进过我房子
Ain't nobody been there but you. Nobody came in my house but you.
一个也没有
Everybody.
就你一个 你是唯一进过我房子的
Nobody but you. You're the only person that came in my house.
说说 你还有什么?
So, what you got going for you?
一无所剩 都抽光了
Ain't got nothing left, burnt it away.
家里人呢?
Family?
我妈死了 老爹 鬼知道
Mother dead. Father, who the fuck know.
兄弟姐妹呢?
Brothers, sisters?
有个姐姐 让我住地下室...
A sister, she lets me stay in the basement...
但她把门锁了 好让我上不了楼
But she lock the door so I can't go upstairs.
能帮的都帮了吧
About the best she can do for me.
有个孩子 是儿子
Got a kid, a son.
想象我还把一条生命带到这世上来了
Imagine me bringing life into the world.
- 他叫啥? - Keyshawn
- What's his name? - Keyshawn.
他妈妈把他带到新泽西去了 说我不适合带孩子
His mother took him up Jersey way, said I wasn't fit to be with the boy.
我没反对
I didn't disagree.
呃...
Well...
至少你身体还不错
At least you got your health.
为身体不错干杯
Here's to health.
我得了艾滋
I got the bug.
94年起就有了
Had it since '94.
还过给了我老伴
Gave that shit to my old lady.
担心过有没有过给我的宝贝女儿
Worried about passing it on to my baby girl.
幸运的是 还好没有
No, I was spared that at least.
该死 你怎么染上的?
Damn, how do you carry it?
你请求她原谅了?
You ask her forgiveness?
当然了
Of course.
她怎么说?
What she say?
说了该说的
What she needed to say.
听着 别人能原谅你固然好...
Look, forgiveness from other folks is good...
可那些都是别人的话
But ain't nothing but words coming at you from outside.
你要想戒了 首先要原谅你自己
You wanna kick this shit, you got to forgive your own self.
爱自己一点吧 兄弟
Love yourself some, brother.
然后去参加一些集会
And then drag your sorry ass to some meetings.
- 集会? - 你他妈的想听到什么?
- Meetings? - What the fuck you wanna hear?
说你够坚强能自己戒了?
That you're strong enough to do this by yourself?
戒毒是容易的
Getting clean's the easy part.
接下来还要过日子呢
Now comes life.
就是有根橙色线从后头伸出来的那栋
It's this one here with the orange cord coming out of the back.
他们偷另外一栋的电
They're pirating juice from the other house.
你他妈开什么玩笑 我现在是为巴尔通用电气当警察啊?
You fucking gotta be kidding me. Now I'm policing for BGE?
他们还没到 等那小子到了 就把他抓起来
They're not there yet, but when this kid here posts, snatch him up.
在这该死的狗窝外头蹲点 等着一个小混混露面?
Park our asses outside this shit-hole and wait for some little project yo to raise up?
我妈的儿子蠢不了
Mrs. McNulty raised no fools.
袋子里有四个Faidley的蟹肉饼...
Four Faidley's crabcakes in the bag...
箱子里24瓶德国啤酒
24 Dutch beers in the box.
Faidley的?
Faidley's?
你还不赖 McNulty
You all right, McNulty.
我才不管局里那些家伙是怎么说你的
I don't care what all them other fucks downtown say about you.
11-35 什么事?
1 1-35, what's up?
我们的朋友要见个面 地点不变
Our friend wants to meet. Same spot.
知道了 15分钟后到
Copy that, 15 minutes.
这兔崽子犯啥事儿了?
What's the deal with the yo-boy?
他干了什么了?
What'd he do?
误闯我的地盘了
Stumbled into my world.
- 5分钟 快点 - 我得走了
- Five minutes, come on. - I have to go.
- Shardene - 我都说我得走了
- Shardene. - I said, I have to go.
- 给我5分钟都不行? - 不行 现在不行
- I can't have five minutes? - No, not right now.
操!
Fuck!
你有多接近?
How close did you get?
要是Wee Bey没有在最后时刻冒出来 你们就得给那黑鬼收尸了...
Y'all be chalking that nigger if Wee Bey ain't pop up at the last second like....
还记得我们上次的谈话吗?
Remember when we last talked?
按理你得退后 案子让我们来处理
You were gonna lay back, let us work our case.
我说过 我做我能做的
I said, I'd do what I can.
不过 我还是想让你们知道 Avon的人联系上我了...
Still, I thought I might let y'all know Avon's people got in contact...
说他们要停止这次争斗
Talking about they want to end the beef.
还给了我某种赦免
They offered me some kind of amnesty.
赦免?
Amnesty?
只要我不再搞什么追杀
Look, I chill out on the manhunt
不再动手抢他们的东西
And stop hitting them in the head for their product,
他们会取消悬赏
They gonna call off the bounty.
那就停战吧 Omar
Take the truce, Omar.
我会的 只要他们不是在耍我
I might, if they ain't trying to play me.
他们说要谈判
They said they want to parley on it.
谈判?
Parley?
听着 我不知道 不过这会儿我要你们帮忙
Look, I don't know, man, but right now I need some assistance from y'all.
我要是去看急诊 Avon就会收到风声...
Yo, son, I go to the ER, and word get back to Avon...
你知道 他就会让他的手下在停车场等我
You know he gonna have his henchmen waiting in the parking lot for me.
我知道你们跟几个医生交情不错 对吧?  对吧?
Look, I know y'all friendly with a couple of doctors, right? Right?
他说他能买到可卡因
He says he can buy weight.
说他为些本地的大佬干活
Says he runs with some decent-size locals.
比如谁?
Like who?
Avon 呃... Barksdale
Avon, something.... Barksdale.
Avon Barksdale?
用DECS和HIDA(两个毒品犯罪档案库)好好查查
Run it through the DECS and HIDA.
看看有什么发现
See what comes back.
我再去问问 看看有没有人办的案子 跟你说的名字有关
I'm gonna check around, see if anybody's working these names you gave us.
你要是瞎扯淡 我一下子就知道
If you full of shit, pal, I'm gonna know it quick.
可你去查找的时候 我怎么办呢?
But what happens to me while you checking?
Eager街
Eager Street.
市监狱去吧 混蛋
City jail, motherfucker.
Blue上周回家去了 之后再没见过他
Blue came home last week. I ain't seen him since.
嗯
Yeah.
难以置信
I can't believe it.
见鬼了 Carv 你啥正事也没干哪
Damn, Carv, you's trifling.
嗯 我承认 我让人讨厌
Yeah, I admit it, I'm disgusting.
奶酪酥还有他妈的Ring-Dings(巧克力派)?
Cheese puffs and fucking Ring-Dings?
嗯
Yeah.
那个在大楼混的大块头...
The big fuck from the high-rise...
他叫啥?
What's his name?
"小个子"
Little Man.
对 是他
Yeah, him.
好的
All right.
唷
Yo.
准备好 要开始了
Be ready, we're on it.
看看这该死的混蛋
Look at this pretty motherfucker.
喝晕了开不了车回家了 McNulty?
Too fucked up to drive home, McNulty?
嘿 Bunk
Hey, Bunk.
那孩子跟我们检举了一起谋杀
Kid gave us a murder.
另外 他还检举了Stringer Bell
More than that, he's put in Stringer Bell.
是嘛?
Yeah?
还指认了Wee-Bey Bird 和Stinkum的照片
Picks out Wee-Bey, Bird and Stinkum from photo arrays.
说他们那晚抓Omar的手下Brandon的时候 三个都在Greek店那
Puts them all up at the Greek's the night they grab up Omar's boy, Brandon.
还说Bell也在车里
Puts Bell in the truck, too.
他说"Stringer要我指认那个抢劫的男孩"
Says, "Stringer told me to point out the stickup boy."
- 天 你们对他干什么了? - 啥都没干
- Jeez, what do you have over him? - Not a fucking thing.
那小子不用逼就全说了
Kid was ready, barely had to push him.
这案子谁负责?
Whose case?
Norris
Norris's.
他多大了?
How old?
16岁
16.
住在Argyle一处废弃的破地方
Lives in a shit-hole vacant over on Argyle.
我去接他的时候 他正晕乎着
When I grab him up, I swear he's halfway into a nod.
吸了?
Using?
杀了那男孩后 这帮狗娘养的就在巷子里弃尸...
When they kill the stickup boy the fuckers dump the body in the alley...
就在那小子和其他混混栖身的平房区后面
Behind where this kid and all the other low-rise hoppers lay their heads.
你能想象吗?
Can you imagine?
他脑子里全是这个
All he can think about.
你告诉他需要他作证了吗?
You tell him he's gonna have to testify?
还没呢 迟早要说的
Not yet, we'll get there.
问题是 现在拿他怎么办?
Problem is, what do we do with him now?
说
Yeah.
大个子接电话了
Big boy picking up.
好的
Okay.
你呼我是吧?
You holler at me, right?
你在哪儿? 我们手头紧了
Where you at, man? We on our way down.
明天一早就到
First thing tomorrow, man.
- 喂? - 就是他 盯住
- Yeah? - It's him, stay on it.
好的
All right.
我啥都没干 让我出去
I didn't do nothing, man, get me outta here.
22 慢慢朝三垒滚去  最后一刻终于中了
The 2-2, grounded slowly towards third, and it gets through at the last moment.
我的电话在哪儿呢?
Where my phone call at?
Suzuki的本垒板 投球了
Suzuki's at the plate, here's the pitch.
一垒打 正中间 Suzuki的本垒打
Line drive, up the middle, a base hit for Suzuki.
Suzuki在场上很耐心
Suzuki's very patient at the plate.
是的 是我
Yeah, man, it's me.
猜猜谁进来了
Guess who's up in here.
那个俱乐部里拉皮条的Orlando
Pimping-ass Orlando, from the club.
对 "场边"
Yeah. Courtside.
你这样瞎混有多久了?
So, how long you been slinging?
自从...也许12岁起吧
Since I was, maybe, 1 2.
你跟着平房区Barksdale那群人多久了?
And how long were you with Barksdale's crew in the low-rises?
跟D'Angelo吗?
With D'Angelo?
没多久
Not long.
他是夏天开始的时候从高楼区过来的
He came down from the towers at the beginning of the summer.
在那之前我替Ronnie Mo干
Before that I worked for Ronnie Mo.
D'Angelo有没有跟你说起过221楼里发生了什么...
D'Angelo ever talk to you about what happened in the 221 building...
Pooh中枪的那次?
With Pooh getting shot?
其他类似的事情呢?
How about anything else like that?
比如什么?
Like what?
杀戮 谋杀
Killings, murders.
他说起东边有幢公寓里 一个女孩中枪的事吗?
He say anything about a girl getting shot in an apartment up on the Eastside?
他...
He--
没有 Dee对我挺好
No, Dee, he was good to me.
他挺好的
He all right.
但D'Angelo...
But D'Angelo,
当晚你在Greek店里看到那个男孩时 你就是打电话给他的吧?
He was who you called that night when you saw the stickup boy at the Greek's, right?
嗯 不过他没上那儿去
Yeah, but he didn't go up there.
主要还是那些大楼里的人
It was mostly those tower boys.
还有Stringer
And Stringer.
你说过Stringer在车里
You said Stringer was in the truck.
他打电话给你
He called you over,
要你指认那个男孩
Asked you to point out the stickup boy.
都有寻呼机的记录做佐证呢...
All of it corroborated by the beeper logs...
还有那个公用电话的笔录
And the pen registers from the project pay phones.
Stinkum死了 Gant的命案 我们也知道是Bird干的
Stinkum's dead. We've already got Bird for the Gant killing.
- 这样就把他们都一网打尽了 - 还有D'Angelo
- This ties them all in. - D'Angelo, too.
也许 但既然他没有在Greek店里出现...
Maybe, but since he didn't show at the Greek's...
他就可以告诉陪审团 他没料到会杀人
He tells the jury he didn't see the murder coming.
但凭这些起诉他也够了
It's enough to charge him, anyway.
父母的情况?
Parents?
母亲酗酒 居无定所 没有固定地址
Alcoholic mother. In the wind, no fixed address.
他说他在东岸有个祖母...
Says he's got a grandmother on the Eastern Shore...
不过好几年没见过她了
But he hasn't seen her in years.
旅馆开个房间?
How about a hotel room?
谁出钱?
On whose dime?
副警长不可能同意安排人力 去保护一个16岁的...
No way the Deputy approves the manpower to stash a 16-year-old...
弄个旅馆房间就更别提了
Much less the room service.
McNulty 2号线电话
McNulty, Line 2.
要不你把这个报告给上头?
How about you run this up to front office?
看看检察官批不批
See if the state's attorney will kick in.
他可是个孩子 Cedric
He's a kid, Cedric.
就算我们搞掂了钱的事 你真想把一个少年安置到...
Even if we clear the money, do you really wanna put a juvenile...
一个旅馆里呆上六个月 等待开庭之日么?
In a hotel for six months waiting on a trial date?
我觉得你们得跟他奶奶联系
I think you all need to get with Grandma down on the shore.
现在? 她要现在?
Now? She's doing this right now?
他们不必安排聆讯日期什么的吗?
They don't have to set a hearing date or something like that?
天哪 好的 好吧
Christ, yeah, okay.
好的
Yeah.
我他妈的需要个该死的律师
I fucking need a fucking lawyer.
怎么了?
What?
你们可以看到 他们有安全栅栏
Still, you can see that they got the security bars
看那儿
And look there.
摄像头 监视院子还有街上
Cameras that see over the yard out to the street.
我跟Verizon通信公司了解过了 这个地址没有安装电话
And I checked with Verizon, there's no phone service at that address.
这可是此地无银三百两
That's a telltale right there.
所以 我们得搜查这地方 对吧?
So what? We try to write a warrant for this place, right?
对吧?
Right?
你在看什么?
What are you seeing?
没有规律 真的
No pattern, really.
除了这一连串的旧店面和仓库...
Except this cluster of old storefronts and warehouses ...
分布在市中心西端
on the west side of downtown.
主要在Paca Utah和Howard街附近
Around Paca, Utah, Howard Street, mostly.
店面?
Storefronts?
通常都是空置的
Vacants, usually.
三家不同的控股公司
Three different holding companies.
- Pryzbylewski警官 - 怎么?
- Detective Pryzbylewski. - What?
按图索骥你很有天分
You have a gift for the paper trail.
不过我们明天需要到街上执行任务 你准备好上街了吗?
Tomorrow calls for some street work, though. Are you street ready?
你知道中尉要我呆办公室里
You know the Lieutenant has me in-office.
得等大陪审团有定论 我才能配枪
I don't have my gun until the grand jury.
不需要的
You won't need one.
上街执行任务? 没有枪?
On the street? No gun?
没有枪
No gun.
这次不用
Not for this.
而且 McNulty先生利用他的儿子们...
Furthermore, Mr. McNulty, having utilized his sons...
执行出警任务 还牵涉一个疑犯...
In an act of police work involving a criminal suspect...
而且就在一个拥挤的市场里 把儿子们弄丢了
Actually lost track of them in a crowded municipal market.
这是令人十分不能接受的 法官大人
This is simply unacceptable, Your Honor.
就算那样 紧急申请法院单方面的限制令
Be that as it may, an emergency ex parte order
也是非常特殊的请求啊 Palmer先生
Is an extraordinary request, Mr. Palmer.
你要我把探访时间限制在下午
You actually want me to limit visitations to afternoons only,
还要求探访时McNulty太太全都在场? 得了吧
And you want Mrs. McNulty present at all visitations? Come on.
这不是个单纯的小失误 法官大人
It is not a single lapse, Judge.
McNulty先生多次无法履行照顾义务
Mr. McNulty has time and again failed to properly care for the children...
在他照看孩子们的时候
When they're in his custody.
我有近期一连串事实的记录 法官大人 足以申请这样的限制令
I have a list of recent events, Your Honor, that justify an order.
Pearlman小姐 你有什么要回应的吗?
Ms. Pearlman, you have a response you'd like to offer up here?
没有
Nope.
什么回应都没有?
Nothing?
如果这是一起故意占有他人财物的诉讼
If this were possession with intent,
那我肯定会准备好提起公诉
I'd be a prosecutor with a plan.
可一次家庭限制令的聆讯?
But a domestic order hearing?
法官大人 我就真是无能为力了
Your Honor, I'm officially clueless.
事实上 作为一名政府雇员 我是不该到这儿来的
In fact, as an employee of the state, I should not actually be here.
好吧 听着 各位...
All right, listen up, people...
在你们要求我 对一起紧急诉讼作出裁决之前...
Before you have me make a ruling on an emergency petition...
每一个人都需要来一个深呼吸
Everybody here just needs to take a deep breath.
字面上的意思 来吧
Literally, come on.
现在 McNulty先生能否跟McNulty太太 进行一个友好的谈话?
Now, then, is Mr. McNulty capable of having a civil conversation with Mrs. McNulty?
能 法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
McNulty太太又能否 跟McNulty先生好好谈谈?
And is Mrs. McNulty equally capable of having a conversation with Mr. McNulty?
可以
Yes.
很好 我要去吃午饭了
Good, then I'm going to lunch.
等我回来 看看我们这法庭...
Let's see when I return if we can't busy this court...
能否有个比McNulty的家里事 更招人爱的案子
With something just a little more engaging than the problems of the McNultys.
听着 起诉是针对我的 我明白 我会承担的
Look, the charge is on me. I understand that, I'll carry that.
但我们的人至少可以
But the least our people can do is
弄点钱去付给担保人
Throw down a little something to pay the bondsman.
这是俱乐部的转让协议
That's the deed of transfer for the club.
还有关于酒类销售的许可证转让的申请
The other thing is a license transfer application for the liquor board.
两份东西的日期都写成上星期
They're both backdated and notarized for last week.
什么?
What?
幌子的底子要干净
A front has to be clean.
不过现在 你不是了
And right now, you ain't that.
签吧
Sign.
我的保释金要先付了
I want my bail paid.
派个保释担保人给我 我就签
You send me a bondsman, I'll sign.
这是你要我告诉他的?
Is that what you want me to tell him?
说我要你签而你不肯?
That I asked you to sign and you wouldn't?
你不是要玩这个游戏吗?
You wanted to be in the game, right?
现在你玩上了
Now you're in the game.
简直难以相信 你居然跟她一块儿来的?
Unbelievable. You show up with her?
Elena 你单方面提起紧急诉讼
Elena, you went for an emergency ex parte.
所以我只能就近找个律师
I grabbed whatever lawyer was standing around.
她就在你附近?
She was standing?
问她要不要把照片拿回去
Ask her if she wants the pictures back.
我想想 我有你跟她在餐馆的照片 你在帮她拉椅子
Let's see, I've got her at the restaurant with you pulling out her chair.
我有她在汽车旅馆的停车场的照片 你当时正帮她开车门...
I've got her at the motel parking lot with you opening the car door for her...
你现在他妈的倒成了绅士了
Because you're such a fucking gentleman now.
真不敢相信你竟雇了Buckman
I can't believe you hired Buckman.
那混蛋一次案子也没办成
Son of a bitch never made a case that counted.
但他就抓到你出轨了
He caught your cheating ass.
Elena 我们上这儿干嘛来了?
Elena, why are we here?
因为你不能让Sean和Michael跟罪犯在一起
Because you can't have Sean and Michael around criminals.
你也不能在一个巴尔的摩的市场里 把他们弄丢了
You can't lose them in a Baltimore market.
这就是原因
That's why.
他不是罪犯
He wasn't a criminal.
我认识那家伙
I know the guy.
我们是在玩游戏
It was a game we were playing.
那可是在白天拥挤的街道上 他们本能够跟踪AI Capone(黑手党教父)
It was daylight on a crowded street. They could've been following AI Capone.
一切本来会很顺利的
It would've been fine.
听着 Elene 他们是我的儿子
Look, Elena, these are my sons.
我爱他们
I love them.
你听见了吗 我爱他们
Do you hear, I love them.
我不会让他们受到伤害的
I'm not gonna let them get hurt.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
还爱着你
Still do.
她知道我雇侦探和拍照的事吗?
Does she know about the detective and the pictures?
不 我干嘛要告诉她?
No, why would I tell her about that?
那么 你们俩还....
And are the two of you still....
没
No.
是的
Yes.
一点点
A little.
来吧 让法官看到我们好好的
Come on, let's make nice for the judge.
好吧
Okay.
我们知道我们还有一个月时间 我们不会放弃的
We know we have a month more to go and we're not gonna let up.
我们要多筹些 我们多花些...
We are going to raise more, we are going to spend more...
到了选举日 我们会出去...
And on Election Day, we are going to be out there...
到每一个选区争取选票
Pushing the vote in every precinct.
你准备好了?
You ready?
来吧 得先吃晚饭
Come on, we'll get dinner first.
还不太饿
Ain't so hungry.
来吧
Come on.
你吸多少?
How much were you using?
我是在问你会不会在我车里吐
I'm asking if you're gonna be sick in my car.
偶尔一小瓶
A cap now and then.
只是鼻吸?
You just snorting?
一两天后就没事了
You'll be all right in a day or two.
来吧
Come on.
那家伙来还是不来 伙计?
This nigger coming or what, man?
他说只要我保证是谈判 他就会出现 我这不来了
Said he would, if I guaranteed a parley. And I'm here on it.
当然他说你会付我酬金 而不是他来付
Of course, he said you would be paying my fee rather than his own self.
你的酬金?
Your fee?
我就像那种婚姻顾问一样
I'm doing like one of them marriage counselors.
按小时收费 告诉某个笨蛋 他该带花儿回家
Charge by the hour to tell some fool he need to bring some flowers home.
然后再多收一小时费用 告诉那个婊子...
Then charge another hour telling the bitch...
她应该不时舔舔他的鸡巴
She ought to suck some cock every little once and a while.
才可以让婚姻关系更牢固
To keep a marriage strong like that.
说到舔鸡巴的
Speaking of cocksuckers.
真不敢相信我们见面了
Don't believe we met.
我是Proposition Joe
Proposition Joe.
你要是敢耍我 我就杀了你全家
You ever steal from me, I kill your whole family.
好了
All right.
你们都来了 我做担保人 规矩点 想什么就都说吧
You all both here on my guarantee, so respect that shit and say what you feel.
我先走了
I'm up out of here.
我碰到一个人 说他愿意留着你的小命
I got a man who say he gonna give you your life back.
谁 Barksdale吗?
Who, Barksdale?
我的人说 "告诉那个该死的混蛋..."
My man say, "Tell that motherfucker that...
"要是他能不打我们口袋的主意..."
"if he can find a way not to dip in our pockets...
"这事咱就算扯平了"
"we're gonna call this shit even."
你们先做了Bailey 又对我手下那样
You all aced Bailey, and what you did to my boy?
你们以为你们对Brandon干了那事之后 我们的恩怨还能扯平吗?
So, y'all think after what you did to Brandon we supposed to find some even on this?
我啥也不知道 明白吗?
I don't know shit about shit, all right?
我只负责传话
I'm just the messenger.
随便你
Whatever, man.
你知道双方都死了人 对吧?
You know there's dead on both sides, right?
要是这争斗持续下去 还会死更多人
And there's gonna be a whole lot more if this beef keep up.
但说实话
But the truth be told,
有一边的人可比另一边多 你知道我在说什么吧?
There be more soldiers on one half than the other. You know what I'm saying?
听着 小子 你告诉Barksdale...
Look here, son, you tell Barksdale...
说他已经为对我手下所作的事付出代价了
That he's been paid back for what he did to my peoples.
但他的货嘛 是人总得谋生的 对吧?
But as for his product, a man's got to earn a living, you know?
我不认识什么叫Barksdale的
I don't know nobody called Barksdale, B.
我说的那个人可不会同意 他的货被人这么搞的
The man I'm talking about can't have his shit taken like that.
那不行
That won't do.
好吧
All right,
那么告诉他给我点钱
Tell him to throw me some cash then,
比方说....
And we'll see....
5千 或1万
About $5,000 or $10,000.
你知道我说什么 退休金 哥们
You know what I mean, for my retirement, homes.
5千块 要是你不再生事的话
$5,000 ifyou can keep quiet about it.
把钱给Joe让他给我
Send my money through Joe, man.
要是通过Joe 你可能连两千都拿不到
You go through Joe, you're not gonna see $2,000 of that.
你干嘛不跟我的人说说你住哪...
Why don't you tell my man where you at--
不行
No.
我们再想法子 你听到了没?
We gonna figure something else out, you hear?
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch, homes.
Stringer Bell太小心了
How careful is Stringer Bell?
"我不认识叫Barksdale的"
"I don't know no one named Barksdale."
见鬼
Shit.
我们还是拿到 他跟Brandon的命案有关的证据了
Still, we got him tied to the Brandon killing.
今天总算没白费功夫
That can be enough for one day's work.
能办的我都办了
Did what I could for y'all.
你确定吗?
You sure, right?
嗯 我九岁的时候在这儿呆了一个夏天
Yeah, I spent a summer here when I was nine.
他们最后一次见到你是什么时候?
When was the last time they saw you?
九岁的时候
When I was nine.
那是什么?
What's that?
什么?
What?
那噪声
That noise.
是蟋蟀
It's crickets.
蟋蟀
Cricket.
Crickets.
他又想捞我的钱?
He try to go in my pockets again?
那黑鬼说要5千
This nigger is talking about $5,000, B.
见鬼
Shit.
怎么了 宝贝?
What's up, baby?
Antwon说把这个拿上来 你还要别的吗?
Antwon said to bring these up. You want anything else?
不用了 很好
No, we cool.
我是说 我们怎么付这钱呢?
I'm saying though, how we supposed to pay that?
他说可以通过Joe 不过我说 去它的Joe
He talking about going through Joe, but I'm like, fuck Joe.
谢谢 你知道我的意思吧?
Thank you, you know what I mean?
你看上去真漂亮 服务也周到
You look good and your services are appreciated.
让他们多给点小费 希望你能挣更多 宝贝
Keep them tips, I hope you making them, baby.
让那狗娘养的到大楼里来...
Make the motherfucker come down to the towers...
拿他剩下的钱 知道我说啥吗?
To get the rest of his money, know what I'm saying?
要是他蠢到敢去高楼区 他就玩完了
If he's stupid enough to come to the towers, he gonna get got.
就这么结了 我们该怎么给呢?
It's a wrap. How we supposed to pay that?
干啊
All right.
你们都以为自己能出来混 可是瞧瞧...
Y'all think you can hang, but, look.
不行
No.
不 你们看看 我上的是新闻学院哦 知道吧?
No, you see, I went to journalism school. All right?
西北大学的 玩这个你们不是我的对手
Northwestern. So you all can't stay with me on this....
你说得你就像什么暴戾的老记者似的
Girl, you talking like you some crusty old reporter.
什么?
Excuse me?
混蛋 你可是在电视台工作的
Bitch, you work at a TV station.
都一样 好不?
It's the same thing, all right?
好吧 别说了
Look, come on, stop talking.
喝吧
Here we go.
喝啊
Bring it.
快 Kima
Come on, Kima.
我明天还得上班呢
I gotta work tomorrow.
胆小鬼
Candy ass.
我只能这么说
That's all I have to say.
好了 看到了?
Okay, you see?
- 我支持你 - 好的
- I'm with you. - All right.
看看Tanya 她还是开画廊的呢
Look at Tanya. And she run a damn art gallery.
你知道 这城市的警察都是孬种
You see, police in this town ain't about shit.
- 我想不是吧 - 谢谢
- Guess not. - Thank you.
一杯酒都喝不了
Can't hold a liquor.
一个面包圈都吃不下
Can't hold a donut.
要是你问我 我想我们...
And if you ask me, I guess we...
在床上的表现也不咋样
Ain't good in bed, either.
别提这茬 警官
Don't go there, Officer.
别提这茬
Don't go there.
Kima 你怎么知道你想当警察?
Kima, how did you know you wanted to be a cop?
你是怎么做出这个选择的?
I mean, how did you choose that?
你小的时候想过吗 还是....
When you were little, did you think about it at all, or....
说啊 Kima
Come on, Kima.
我记得我在北东区的时候 还是个警校学员 在做实战训练
I remember when I was in the Northeast, still field-training as a cadet.
不知道自己会不会坚持下去
I didn't know if I was gonna stick with it or not.
然后就接到了一个任务
And then we got this one call.
我们追着一个抢钱包的 进入了几座公寓
We chased this purse-snatcher up into these apartments.
我跟我的指导员失散了
I got separated from my FTO.
见鬼 我那时还不是警察
Shit, I ain't even no police yet.
你们知道 只是个学员罢了
You know, I'm just a trainee.
可就落单了
And I'm alone.
可我也不知怎的 就找到了这个家伙
Anyway, I mean, I don't know how, but I find the guy.
我抓到了他 紧紧抓住他 然后拿起了我的无线电对讲机
So I catch him and I hold on to him and I manage to get to my radio.
我们在停车场的中央 在地上打滚...
We in the middle of this parking lot and we're rolling around...
这该死的家伙不停踢着我的屁股 想逃之夭夭
And this motherfucker's steady kicking my ass trying to get away.
我张望了一下  看到了黑色皮靴和蓝色的制服裤
I look over and I see these black patents and these uniform blue pants.
我一抬头就看见了Charlie Smoot...
I look up and it's Charlie Smoot...
他妈的Charlie Smoot 他可是个传奇人物
Charlie fucking Smoot. You know, this guy's a legend.
他低头看着我 笑着 很沉着的
He looks down at me and he smiles, you know real quiet-like.
然后他扔下手铐
And he drops his cuffs.
说"给你的 菜鸟"
He says, "Here you go, rook."
他就只说了这句
That's all he says.
"给你 菜鸟"
"Here you go, rook."
然后他把手铐扔下就走了
And then he dropped the bracelets and walked away.
我知道你们不喜欢听
I mean, I know you don't like it.
但我当时自豪极了
But shit, I was proud.
该死的
God damn.
Lester说我们拿不到这地方的搜查令
Lester says we ain't gonna write a warrant on this place.
有这些玩意儿怎么就拿不到搜查令?
How do we not with all this PC?
我们要查的是他们的老窝 对吧?
We're on the main stash, right?
我们何必还要破门而入呢...
Why would we kick the door in...
既然我们只要把车停在街边...
When all we have to do is park a van down the street...
就能追踪整个西区毒品的流向
Follow the entire Westside drug supply in and out of the place?
我们要开始了解Barksdale的整个世界...
We're gonna start picking up pieces of Barksdale's world...
我们之前从未了解的部分
We never even knew about.
找你们找的好惨
Been hell looking for you people.
你们这小组到底叫什么?
What the hell's the name of this unit anyway?
见鬼 Kima也在呢
Shit, Kima in the house.
怎么了 Wig? 刑事调查组的 从Pikesville冒出来了
What's up, Wig? State police, CID, out of Pikesville.
他叫Troy Wiggins 不过别理他...
Name of Troy Wiggins, but pay no attention to the man...
他可是个彻头彻尾的混蛋
Because he about 90-95% pure bullshit.
Kima 她那么说是因为 她年轻时我跟她有过一腿
Kima, she just talk like that because I had her when she was good.
去你的 是你这该死的家伙不要我的
Shit, you the ugly-ass motherfucker turned me the other way.
去 好了
Shit, all right.
我跟各位说说这事
Here's the thing, boys and girls.
我在Arundel冒充毒贩进行交易
I'm doing a reverse buy-down in Arundel, right?
抓到一个西区的混蛋要买四盎司毒品
And I get this Westside asshole nibbling on four ounces, right?
才四盎司?
A whole four ounces?
我知道 他不是大鱼 不过...
I know, he ain't much, but...
我把他抓进去 他就什么都说了...
I get him in the boat and he starts flopping around...
说他能从一个叫Barksdale的手里买可卡因
Saying he can buy weight from some motherfucker, name of Barksdale.
我没听说过Barksdale
I never heard of no Barksdale.
不过我在DECS系统里查了
But I put the name into DECS.
计算机说Avon Barksdale 是巴尔的摩市主要的打击目标
And the computer has Avon Barksdale entered as an active Baltimore city target.
我去了缉毒处 Dawson...
So I go down to City Narcotics, and Dawson,
让我来这儿找你们
He sends me down here to see y'all.
你抓的那条鱼叫啥?
So what's the name of your fish?
Wendell O
Wendell O.,
一个从警察手里买毒品的笨蛋Blocker
As in... oh-shit-l-tried-to-buy from-a-state-police Blocker.
不会是Wendell "Orlando" Blocker吧?
That wouldn't be Wendell "Orlando" Blocker, would it?
是啊 你说对了
Yeah. You on it.
Orlando
Orlando.
后间是锁着的
They keep that back room locked.
就算我有事进去
And even if I do get back there on an errand,
他们立刻就闭嘴了 很谨慎的
Then they kind of shut down. They get real quiet.
你说听到有一个人说起...
You said you heard one say something about...
要让某个人到高楼区去
Making someone come into the towers.
对
Yeah.
说话的是谁?
Which one was talking?
他挺高的
He was tall, I think.
好吧 还有谁?
All right, but who else was there?
不戴眼镜我真的看不清
I don't really see that well without my glasses.
你的眼镜呢?
Where are your glasses?
没有眼镜你连脸都看不清?
You can't see faces without those?
你上班的时候不戴眼镜 对吧?
You don't wear those while you're working, do you, darling?
你会吗?
Would you?
我是靠卖酒和小费挣钱的
I gotta live off drinks and tips.
不可能
No way.
怎么不可能?
Why not?
因为不可能让一个毒贩子 做贩酒执照上的法人
Because a player wouldn't be the name on the liquor license.
他要是能接触Barksdale的可卡因
He'd have a connect for Barksdale's coke.
就不会中了警察的圈套
He wouldn't walk into state troopers.
他背着一条罪状呢 只是想给自己脱罪
He got a charge and now he's talking out his ass.
面对现实吧 你永远也抓不到Avon或者Stringer跟毒品同处一室
You're never gonna get Avon or Stringer in the same room as the dope.
我们只能靠监听他们的行动
We make this case on their voices alone.
那么 也许他是不能从Barksdale那买入
So maybe he can't buy from Barksdale.
也许他只能向Savino或Wee-Bey买呢
Maybe he can only buy from Savino or Wee-Bey.
那就去他的
Fuck him, then.
我们已经查明Wee-Bey跟谋杀有关
We already got Wee-Bey tied to a murder,
而Savino不过是个小跟班
And Savino's the runt of the litter.
Orlando提供的俱乐部的证词可以采信
We can take what Orlando gives us about the club.
也许还有洗钱 或者是涉黄的事
The money laundering, maybe, or the girls.
那样的合作可以减几年刑 就扯平了
For that kind of cooperation, I'll drop a few years and call it fair.
Daniels在吗?
Daniels in here?
在
Yeah.
副局长来电找你
Call from Deputy Commissioner for you.
要在这儿听吗?
You want it in here?
不
No.
他没错过多少嘛
He doesn't miss much.
我需要些帮助
I need some help here.
得了 Bubs
Come on, Bubs.
你让我放下工作穿过整个城市来见你...
You got me coming across town in the middle of a fucked-up workday...
就是为了拿10块钱 这可不对
Just so you can hold $10, that shit ain't right.
等等 我不要10块钱 知道吧?
Hold on, I don't need $10, okay?
我不知道 我要一个自己的住处
I don't know. I need a place of my own.
行吗? 一张床 一些床单和一些衣服
All right? Some bed, some sheets, some clothes.
我真的需要些新衣服
I definitely need some new clothes.
多久没吸了?
How long you been clean?
三天
Three days.
你是来真的?
You serious about it?
谁知道呢?
Who knows?
我该拿一个戒了毒的线人怎么办?
What the fuck am I gonna do with a clean informant?
你想过这个吗?
Did you think about that?
好吧 我挺你
All right, I'm on it with you.
真的?
Yeah?
真的
Yeah.
怎么了 表示一下啊
What the fuck, give me some love.
好吧 我要一张床垫 自己的地方...
Okay, I mean, I think I can get, you know, a mattress, my own place...
大概几百块钱的东西
Everything for like a couple hundred dollars.
好吧 我们谈谈
All right. We'll talk.
我今晚还要去一个地方 明天再呼我
I gotta be somewhere tonight, so hit me on my page tomorrow.
明天?
Tomorrow?
有我呢
I got you.
污点证人说他能买到可卡因
The cooperator says he can buy weight.
但不是从Barksdale或Bell那
Not from Barksdale or Bell.
你怎么确定呢?
How can you be sure?
要多少毒品才能让Avon Barksdale现身呢?
How much dope or coke do you think gets Avon Barksdale into the room?
一公斤?
A kilo?
两公斤? 二十公斤?
2 kilos? 20 kilos?
靠诱捕是动不了高层的
We are not going to buy our way up the ladder here.
这样的人不接触毒品 他们从来不会靠近毒品
These people do not touch the drugs. They don't go near the drugs.
只有监听才让我们发现了Barksdale
The wire is what gives us Barksdale.
发现了整个团伙
It gives us the whole crew.
一天天 一点点
Day by day, piece by piece.
诱捕 中尉
Buy-bust, Lieutenant.
是我几个月前就跟你提议的
It's what I asked you for months ago.
我们做得蛮成功...
It's what we do successfully...
一再地破获些案子
Time and again to make these cases.
为什么选纽约?
Why New York?
那里精彩着呢 这么大座城 你知道我说什么吧?
Must be something happening out there. Too big a town, you know what I mean?
你不相信他们要停战?
You don't believe in the truce?
所以我才提出要钱
That's why I asked for that money.
要是他说了 "钱我们不给 能活着就满足吧"
If he had said, "We ain't paying, just be happy to live"...
我倒会觉得他们还挺真的
I'd have been like, they keeping it real.
可他说上门去取5千 我想 得了吧
But he say, come on down for $5,000. I'm, like, man, please.
我说 听着 我没多少要求 不过旅费上我有点拮据
Look here, homes, I ain't asked for much, but I'm a little light on traveling money.
我是说我可以上街道自己弄点钱  但我在想...
I'm saying, I could go around the block and get myself paid, but I'm thinking.
大家用呼机保持联络
You keep in touch with my pager.
Gant案子的诉讼我们还需要你呢
We're gonna need you for the Gant trial.
悠着点 Omar
Go easy, Omar.
别被抓了
Stay free.
你在Lex和Fulton交接的折扣店外头接我
You be picking me up outside the cut-rate on Lex and Fulton.
10点后我会到 可以吧?
I be up there after 10.:00, right?
可以
That'll work.
听着 各位
Listen up, people.
我们有三万块毒资 通过药品管理局的朋友们筹的
We've got $30,000 in buy money, courtesy of our friends over at DEA.
问题是 他们不能让钱跑了
But the thing is, they can't have that money walking on them.
绝对不行
Definitely not.
所以由Kima在车里卧底  实施诱捕
So Kima will be in the car for the buy, fronting as our Cl's girl.
也得看好了
Looking the part, too.
你的枪放哪儿?
Now, where's your weapon gonna be?
他也许会搜我身 所以枪得藏车里
He might pat me, so it has to stash in the car.
我想等Savino在折扣店那儿上车...
I figure when Savino gets in the car at the cut-rate...
我就到后座去
I'll be going in back.
枪就放后座底下
It'll be up under the rear seat.
我们也许不能太靠近 监视到整个过程...
And we probably can't be close enough for an eyeball on this...
但车上会放窃听器
But the car will be a live wire.
Kima一有机会就会通知所在方位
And Kima will be throwing us 20s whenever she can.
Rhonda
Rhonda.
我只想提醒Blocker先生...
I only want to remind Mr. Blocker here...
他的减刑是视他的合作程度而定的
That his plea agreement is contingent on cooperation.
诱捕Savino Bratton的合作性...
And a buy-bust on Savino Bratton is less cooperative...
就不如诱捕一个高层头目那么大了
Than a buy-bust from someone higher up on the food chain.
要是能让Savino谈论Avon或Stringer...
If you can get Savino talking about Avon or Stringer...
那对我们 对你都好
That's better for us and better for you.
他们都知道他被诱捕了 对吧?
They already know that he got jacked on a reverse buy, right?
怎么不会以为他已经告密了呢?
Why wouldn't they assume he's snitching?
我需要钱请律师 对吧?
I need money for a lawyer, right?
就是这个理由
That's the story.
他被捕了 然后现在要重操旧业...
He got popped and now he needs to get right back into it...
因为要付担保人和律师费
To pay the bondsman and the lawyer.
好的
All right.
行动吧
Let's make this work.
小心点
Careful.
你拿的可是我的饭碗
That's my career you're holding there.
- 有车吗 - 在中层楼呢
- You got a unit? - Parked in the mezzanine.
- 钥匙给我 - 不行 我开车 该死的
- Give me the keys, man. - No, I'm driving, motherfucker.
来啊
Come on, man.
这儿可是"死囚区"
Death row here.
还没完呢
Ain't up.
"死囚区"
Death row.
折扣店
我的妞
My girl.
一半钱是她的
Half the money's hers.
宝贝 我们既然要走北大道...
Baby, since we going down North Avenue...
找个店停一下 我好买点烟
Stop by the carry-out so I can pick me up some cigarettes.
他们在往北走 别跟太紧
They're going up North, stay loose.
见鬼 太大声了
Shit. It's too loud.
没有哪个小组看得到吗?
Does any unit have the eyeball?
没有 11-35
Negative, 1 1-35.
快啊 Greggs 告诉我们你在哪里
Come on, Greggs, tell us where the fuck you are.
那边停
Pull in there.
- 什么? - 那边停
- What? - Pull in there.
别少了数
Don't fuck with this count.
我马上带你的东西回来
I'll be right back with your shit.
我们在哪儿?
Where are we?
路标说是Longwood 但我发誓这是Warwick
That sign said Longwood, but I could swear this was Warwick.
那些混混就喜欢弄乱路牌糊弄人
Hoppers be turning the sign poles to fuck with you all.
我觉得我们在Warwick北端 一条巷子里....
I make it we're on the north side of Warwick, in an alley....
我不知道 见鬼
I don't know, shit.
Longwood向西半个街区 也许是
Half a block west of Longwood, maybe?
希望你们都听到了
I hope you all copy that.
嗯 我们离你八个街区远呢
Yeah, that puts us about eight blocks away.
得再靠近些
I'm pushing in a little closer.
所有小组注意
All units be advised.
在Warwick 靠近Longwood 北侧巷子 或是靠近20街
Warwick near Longwood in the north side alley. Or near that 20.
你们感觉对头吗
This got the right feel for you?
再靠近些?
You creeping closer?
他最好不要太久 因为我不知道窝点在哪儿...
He better not be long, because I don't know where the stash is...
要是他们一路带我们穿过这城市
And if they dragging us all over this part of town--
那是什么?
What's that?
什么?
What?
有些不太对劲
Something ain't right.
- 什么? - 不对劲
- What? - Shit ain't right.
你这告密的混蛋
You snitching motherfucker.
求救! 求救!
Signal 13, signal 13!
发生枪击...
Gunshots...
枪击 全市通告 11-35
Gunshots. Go city-wide. 11-35.
- 11-35 - 请求支援 Warwick...
- 11-35. - Signal 13. Warwick...
在Longwood附近 有警员中枪
Near Longwood, officer down.
两个白人 黑人混混 两个 有一个...
Two males, black hoodie, both of them, one is--
请求支援 Warwick Longwood附近 巷子里 检查巷子...
Signal 13, Warwick, near Longwood, in the alleys. Check the alleys...
北边  2800街区 没有发现
Northside, 2800 block. Nothing.
有警员中枪 是个出色的卧底女警
We got an officer down, she's a number one, female undercover.
833小组 方位Baker3100街区以东没有发现
Unit 833, bearing east on 3100 block of Baker. Clear.
2900街区一片漆黑
2900 is dark.
11-35  10-38已响应(设置路障)
11-35, 10-38 is responding.
10-4(收到)
10-4.
11-71 有人看到了吗? 有人看到了吗?
11-71, does anyone have a visual? Does anyone have a visual?
- 呼叫F小队(Baltimore直升机队) - 我们要找什么?
- Foxtrot. - What are we looking for?
11-35呼叫KGA(总台)
1 1-35 to KGA.
找不到中枪警员 需要直升机...
We can't find the officer down. We need Foxtrot...
寻找一辆绿色林肯汽车 带褐色乙烯顶棚
Iooking for a green Lincoln Town Car with a brown vinyl roof,
停在那些巷子里的
Parked in those alleys.
F小队出动 3-14
Foxtrot en route, 3-1-4.
3-14 听着 有警员呼救
3-14, be advised, we have a signal 13.
7820 巡查单数地址一侧
7820, rear odd-side.
Baker 3300街区 没有发现
3300 block of Baker. Clear.
巡查Warwick和Longwood双数地址一侧
Visual, rear even-side of Warwick and Longwood.
请求支援 请求支援 警员中枪
Signal 13, signal 13. Officer down.
SUV车  在Warwick西侧 下一路口右转
SUV, west on Warwick, make the next right.
注意 现场没有动静
Be advised, no movement at scene.
在这儿 叫救护车
In here. Call for a medic.
有警员中枪 要救护车
We got an officer down, we need a medic.
7820 10-23(到达现场) 请求DV
7820, 10-23, give us DV in here.
10-4(收到)
10-4.
医护小组呢 请求援救!
Where the fuck is the medic?Signal 13,
有警员中枪
We got an officer down.
10-38已响应
10-38 is responding.
有体貌描述么?
Do we have a description?
有小组在现场吗?
Any unit on scene?
有疑犯的体貌描述吗?
Do you have a description of the suspect?
10-47(紧急 请求道路维护)
That's a 10-47.
不同领域电台代码有所出入 标注仅供参考